<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Usages on plybuild</title>
    <link>https://plybuild.io/usage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Usages on plybuild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:15:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://plybuild.io/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/usage/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 10:29:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/usage/install/</guid>
      <description>Plybuild is created with Go and supports multiple platforms including:&#xA;GNU/Linux Windows MacOs Download plybuild Install plybuild with one of the two alternatives&#xA;Alternative 1: Binaries Download the latest binaries from https://github.com/DevDimensionLab/plybuild/releases Alternative 2: Brew Add a new tap brew tap devdimensionlab/plybuild Install brew install plybuild Alternative 3: Sources plybuild sources are available at https://github.com/DevDimensionLab/plybuild&#xA;Clone sources git clone https://github.com/DevDimensionLab/plybuild.git Compile and install make install </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/usage/dependencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:15:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/usage/dependencies/</guid>
      <description>plybuild strives to depend on as few third parties as possible, but some dependencies are optional&#xA;Git plybuild uses git for various operations related to cloud-config and templates. Without git installed some functionality might not work as expected.&#xA;Without git A clean Windows 10 installation without git:&#xA;With git git installed on the cmd.exe path with git bash:&#xA;Maven plybuild uses mvn Maven for some analytics commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basics</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/usage/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 12:17:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/usage/basics/</guid>
      <description>Most of the ply commands operate on some common principles, target, recursive, and dry-run.&#xA;--target By default ply operates on the current folder similar to tools like git. However a custom --target flag is available for most commands and enables the used to use ply ... --target outside of the working folder.&#xA;--recursive Recursive mode is enabled with --recursive or -r for most commands. This mode starts by building a list of subprojects on the current target, and iteratively working on each subproject.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
