<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> 2. Commands on plybuild</title>
    <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in  2. Commands on plybuild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:27:03 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://plybuild.io/commands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/profile/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/profile/index.html</guid>
      <description>The profile command in Plybuild is designed for efficient management of different user profiles, each with its unique configurations and settings. This feature allows users to create, modify, and switch between profiles, enabling a seamless transition across various project environments and personal preferences. It&amp;rsquo;s especially useful in collaborative settings or for individuals handling multiple projects, as it simplifies the complexity of managing distinct configurations. The command enhances Plybuilds&amp;rsquo;s customization capabilities, making it a valuable tool for organized and streamlined project management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/build/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:27:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/build/index.html</guid>
      <description>Builds a ply project with ply files and formatting Usage: ply build [flags] ply build [command] Aliases: build, generate Available Commands: add Add templates and functionalities for files to a build example Builds example from cloud-config format Format functionality for a project init Initializes build with ply files and formatting options Prints options on spring version, dependencies etc remove Removes files and folders in a ply build project Flags: --application-name string Overrides applicationName from config file --artifact-id string Overrides artifactId from config file --boot-version string Defines spring-boot version to use --cloud-sync Cloud sync (default true) --config-file string Optional config file (default &amp;#34;ply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Status</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/status/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/status/index.html</guid>
      <description>The status command in Plybuild is a practical and informative feature designed to keep users up-to-date with dependency version information. This command serves as a quick and reliable way to check the current versions of dependencies used in a project, and more importantly, it identifies if there are any outdated versions that need attention. By running the status command, users can effortlessly monitor the health and currency of their project&amp;rsquo;s dependencies, ensuring that all components are running on the latest and most secure versions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/upgrade/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/upgrade/index.html</guid>
      <description>Upgrade is a command for upgrading all or specific parts of a project.
Help Perform upgrade on existing projects Usage: ply upgrade [command] Available Commands: 2party Upgrade all 2party dependencies to project 3party Upgrade all 3party dependencies to project all Upgrade everything in project dependency Upgrade a specific dependency on a project deprecated Remove and replace deprecated dependencies in a project interactive Interactively upgrade the project kotlin Upgrade kotlin version in project plugins Upgrade all plugins found in project spring-boot Upgrade spring-boot to the latest version with-versions Upgrade using mvn versions in a project Flags: --cloud-sync force cloud sync --dry-run dry run does not write to pom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plugin</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/plugin/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/plugin/index.html</guid>
      <description>Plybuild also boasts a versatile plugin section, expanding its functionality beyond the core features. This section enables the integration of additional, specialized features that cater to more specific needs, which might not be necessary for all users but are invaluable for those who require them. The plugin architecture allows for customization and extensibility, letting users tailor the tool to their unique workflows and preferences. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s adding support for different programming languages, integrating with third-party services, or enhancing existing features, the plugin system makes Plybuild adaptable and scalable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://plybuild.io/commands/tips/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://plybuild.io/commands/tips/index.html</guid>
      <description>Help A concentrated version of things you need to know for a topic, typically internal know-how that you can&amp;#39;t find on the internet Usage: ply tips [flags] ply tips [command] Available Commands: list Lists all tips for current profile show Show tips Flags: -h, --help help for tips Global Flags: --debug turn on debug output --doc open documentation website --force uses default for prompts --json turn on json output logging Use &amp;#34;ply tips [command] --help&amp;#34; for more information about a command.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>